Hi friends, welcome to my new
vlog.  So, as part of our NRE series,
today we are going to introduce you to
an
account scheme called ICCI Bank's NRI Pro Program.  Let's take a closer look at the
details and features of the Zoho account
.
Before we do that, let us reiterate that the
terms and conditions that were in place when we made this video are not necessarily the same as the terms and conditions that were in place when
you created this account
.  Therefore, always check
these
details in detail on their
website before opening an account.  I think you will
understand after looking at it.  So
NR Pro is a
premium NR account from ICI.  As
we always do when we start,
let's take a look at its main features.
Importantly, they have said that what they have given is a
feature-rich debit card
.  That is, Visa's
Platinum Debit Card is
included in this scheme.  They have also provided privilege
pricing and other pricing benefits.  Let
's take a closer look at its details
.  As always,
let's start by
setting the minimum balance criteria and taking a look
.  For this, at the
bottom of our page,
under Eligibility, we have provided a detailed explanation of
who is eligible and what the minimum balance is
.  If you have opened an account,
you must maintain a minimum balance of Rs. 2 lakh in this account
.  If that's not enough,
the bank has also given some other options.  This means that if you
have an FD of Rs. 1 lakh in your account, you are
eligible for this account scheme
.  Now, even if we
have that or Rs 25 lakh in our account, deposits, loans, demats, credit card expenses, etc., we are still eligible for this scheme
.  Then the third
option is given as a
housing loan. If
you
have a housing loan above Rs. 1000000 in ICICI Bank, then
you are still eligible to use this scheme.
ICICI has given it there. So, as I
said earlier, it is a premium
account, so in
the case of average monthly balance, everything is
premium. You have to keep a minimum of Rs. 2 lakh as average
monthly balance in this
account. Now, let
's look at the PNL charges.
What happens if you do not keep the minimum balance in the account? It is
said here. So, it is
given here that 3%
of the shortfall is required MAB or 500, whichever is less. That is, if there is a shortfall from the
minimum balance to be maintained,
that shortfall is
3% or 500, whichever is
less.
We have already discussed what shot fall is and how to calculate it in the
previous video.
I will give the link of that video in the i
button above and in the description below.
Now let's talk about the debit card that comes with
this ICICI Bank's Penri Pro account. As I
said earlier, it is
Visa's Platinum Debit Card.
Here
they have given a few things as benefits and features.
Visa Premium
Privileges. Since it is a Visa card,
you can enjoy their premium privileges through this card.
Then there is the fuel
surcharge waiver, that is, if you are paying more than Rs. 400, if you are paying more than
Rs. 401,
they are waived off that surcharge.
Then they have given a lot of features like Shopee Worldwide
Online Transactions, Visa Global Emergency
Service, and so on
.  What
we need to look at most importantly are its daily
limits.  If it is domestic,
that is, within India,
you are permitted daily cash withdrawals of up to Rs. 1 lakh
.
Apart from that, a
daily limit of up to Rs. 2 lakh is also available to you through online or POA swiping
.  When you go to Zo International, the
limit for an online e-commerce transaction is
reduced to one and a half lakh rupees.  Apart from that, they are also offering
two ICICI Rewards points for every Rs 200 purchase
.  So
these are the important debit card
related details.  Now
let's take a look at its AMC charges and
stuff.
They do not charge any annual maintenance charges for the Visa Platinum card on the Free NR Pro account.  Similarly, even if
the card is lost,
they will not charge you
anything.  But they charge
375 as courier charges to send you the card
.
The ATM is now nearby and is being interchanged
.  Transaction at non-ICICI
Bank ATMs is the charge levied when using ATMs of banks other than ICICI
.
They do not charge any kind of fee here.  It is
given as Nil.  But
another interesting thing is that there is no need to pay any charges when using transactions at ICC
Bank ATMs in India, i.e.
ATMs of other banks in India
.  But if the ICC ATM itself
goes above five transactions, they charge Rs. 21, as stated
here
.
There is no charge when using a regular ATM.  There are
charges when using other ATMs
.  Here, on the contrary, there is no
charge when using other ATMs
.  But it is stated that there is a charge when using Ona ATMs
.  Now, if you use this debit
card internationally, that is,
outside India,
they will charge Rs 125 for each cash transaction
.  In addition,
they will also charge a currency convention rate of three and a half percent
.  Similarly, it is also stated here that if you are doing non-
financial transactions, such as balance
checks,
they will charge Rs 25
.  Now, if
you are using it at a POS or ATM that comes under Visa,
Outside
India does not charge any other charges there
.  But
they are charging three and a half percent as currency conversion charges
.  So now let's talk
about the airport lounges that come with this one card
.  That is, ICICI Bank is offering
free domestic airport lounges on this card
.   It is important to
note that this is a facility that you can use at eight airport lounges twice a quarter, meaning annually, and is only available for domestic flights, not international flights.  Now let
's talk about other charges,
namely locker charges, which are said to be 40% of
the discounted annual fee
.  This means that if you
take out a locker, this account holder will get a discount of up to 40%
.
Similarly, there is no charge for issuing a check book
.  But they are charging another
fee, saying it is a courier charge of Rs. 375
.  There are no charges for sending a checkbook or for
collecting checks
.   If it's a
stop payment,
they charge Rs 100 for each stop payment.   If
you are using the digital method, there are no
charges
.
They have waved charges for all these NEFT, IMBS, RTS
Charges have been waived for issuing DD.  Similarly, there is no
charge for setting up a standing instruction
.  No issues duplicate
statement charges.
Some other charges are
given as Decline of
Transaction at any ATM or Point
of Sale due to Insufficient Balance
.  This means that if
you swipe
or try to withdraw money from this card without a balance and the
transaction
fails, the person who charges you for the money has
written it down exactly.  And
you have paid the charges related to ECS standing instructions accurately so far
.  You can
look at it.  So, these are the
important benefits that
ICICI Bank offers to its customers under the NRI Pro program
.  So, if your account
is in ICICI Bank,
comment ICICI.  Also, if
you
liked this video, please leave your
valuable comments
.
You can comment on all your doubts
.  I will reply to it
.
Goodbye until I come back with another video.